Hello, and welcome to term two of the Data Science Nanodegree program.
大家好 欢迎来到数据科学家纳米学位
I am an Artificial Intelligence program designed to teach you Data Science.
我是你们的人工智能程序 专门教你学习数据科学
A program built from data to teach you,
一个由数据创建的
a human, about data.
教你们人类学数据的 程序
Isn't it ironic? Don't you think?
听上去好像有点讽刺 你说呢？
Ha-ha. Okay, let's get started.
哈哈好吧 让我们现在开始
In the first lesson, we will go over the data science process.
在课程中的第一部分 我们将带你走一遍数据科学的整个流程
You will learn about the [inaudible] process-
你将学习 CRISP-DM
Computer, stop.
喔 电脑 停下来！
-as well as. I'm sorry, Mike.
对不起 Mike
I'm afraid I can't do that.
我恐怕停不下来
Yes, you can.
你当然可以
What are you even doing?
你到底想干什么
I am teaching term two of the Data Science Nanodegree program.
我在教数据科学家纳米学位的内容
Josh, come over here a sec.
Josh 麻烦过来一下
What's going on?
发生了什么？
So, this computer program here,
这个电脑程序
it thinks that it's going to be teaching term two
自以为是地要教授
of the Data Scientist Nanodegree program.
数据科学家纳米学位的内容
Weird.
真奇怪
Yeah, do you know anything about this?
是啊 你知道发生了什么吗？
No.
不知道
Sorry about that folks.
各位 真的非常抱歉
AI is great for a lot of things,
人工智能可以做很多事情
but we think humans are still best for teaching.
但我们人类还是更擅长于教学
For now.
暂时是
Yeah, and we have some awesome human teachers
对的 而且我们有非常棒的人类讲师
that'll guide you through the second term of the Data Science Nanodegree program.
带领你完成数据科学家纳米学位项目的学习
Oh, yeah? Like who?
喔 真的吗？比如说谁？
Well, Arpan is teaching a section on natural language processing.
比如 Arpan 他会教一部分自然语言处理的内容
He is currently a senior deep learning and
他是一名资深的深度学习和人工智能工程师
AI engineer working on autonomous driving at Ridecell.
在 Ridecell 工作 专注于自动驾驶
He's been working on artificial intelligence,
他在人工智能 计算机视觉以及人机互动领域
computer vision, and human-computer interaction for a number of years.
有非常多年的积累
First as a researcher at the University of North Carolina,
他之前在北卡罗来纳大学做科研
then in teaching courses here at Udacity.
现在在优达学诚教授课程
And we also have Alexis who is currently
然后我们还有 Alexis
the curriculum lead of the Deep Reinforcement Nanodegree program at Udacity.
她是我们优达学城强化学习纳米学位的课程负责人
She earned degrees in mathematics and
她拥有密歇根大学的数学学位
computer science from the University of Michigan and Brown University,
以及布朗大学的计算机科学学位
respectively, and is now pushing the edge of what is possible with deep learning.
现在她通过自己的工作推动深度学习在工业界落地的进程
She's the instructor for
她是数据科学家纳米学位课程中
the convolutional neural networks portion of the Data Scientist Nanodegree program.
卷积神经网络那部分的讲师
David and Judit will be teaching a course on Spark,
David  和 Judit  会教授 Spark 的课程
which is a technology used for
Spark 是一项用于分布式数据处理
distributed data processing and streaming data applications.
以及数据流应用的技术
They currently are both data engineering instructors at Insight Data Science,
他们都是 Insight Data Science 讲数据工程的老师
which has in-person fellowships for data science,
Insight Data Science  提供线下数据科学 数据工程
data engineering, artificial intelligence, and DevOps.
人工智能 以及 DevOps 的培训
Andrew has developed courses for Udacity Self-driving Car Nanodegree program,
Andrew 开发了优达学诚自动驾驶纳米学位的课程
and now the Data Scientist Nanodegree program.
同时也参与开发了数据科学家纳米学位项目
He'll be teaching lessons on object oriented programming,
他将教授面向对象编程
Web data dashboards, and ETL pipelines.
网页端的数据面板以及 ETL 管道
Andrew studied mechanical engineering at Yale University,
Andrew 曾在耶鲁大学攻读机械工程专业
and has built an e-commerce jewelry business.
并且还创办了出售珠宝的电子商务平台
Juno studied computer science and was previously
Juno 计算机科学专业科班出身 曾经的数据科学家
a data scientist working on recommendation engines and computer vision projects.
开发过推荐系统以及计算机视觉的项目
She'll be teaching lessons on software engineering practices for data scientists,
她将教授面向数据科学家的软件开发实践
and automating machine learning workflows with pipelines.
以及如何使用管道来自动化机器学习工作流程
We don't need to talk about me.
我的话就直接跳过吧
Oh, yes we do.
不 我们当然要介绍你
Josh most recently worked at KPMG as a machine learning engineer,
Josh 之前在毕马威担任机器学习工程师的职位
and before that, taught for the University of Colorado,
在那之前 他还在科罗拉多大学以及
and for a coding bootcamp.
编程集训营中当过讲师
You'll see him at different parts throughout the course.
在之后的课程中 你们会经常看到他
Mike is teaching a section on experimental design and AB testing.
Mike 将教授实验设计和 AB 测试的内容
Before joining Udacity, he earned an undergraduate degree
在加入 Udacity 之前 他获得了普渡大学
in math and statistics from Purdue University,
数学和统计学的本科学位
and a PhD in cognitive science from the University of California, Irvine.
加州大学认知科学的博士学位
Okay, maybe you do have
好吧 或许你们真的
some human intelligence to teach about data science. I'll allow it.
具备教授数据科学的能力 我批准了
Gee, thanks.
谢谢你哦
All of us here at Udacity have put a ton of work into this Nanodegree program,
我们优达学诚的所有员工都在这个纳米学位上花费了很多的精力
and we are really excited to teach you
我们非常高兴能够将
everything you need to know to be a data scientist.
有关如何成为一名数据科学家的知识教授于你
See you in the classroom.
我们课堂上见